Narrator: Inspector Granger arrived at about nine o’clock.
He was a short man with white hair and pale blue eyes.
Amanda, Barbara, Claudia, and Gordon were in the living room.
The inspector came in.
Inspector: Mr. Travers died between midnight last night and seven o’clock this morning.
Narrator: He said.
Inspector: Somebody in this room killed him.
Narrator: He looked at them one by one, but nobody spoke.
Inspector: Mrs. Travers, I want to talk to you first.
Come into the study with me, please.
Narrator: Amanda followed the inspector into the study, and they sat down.
Inspector: What did your husband do after dinner last night?
Amanda: We finished dinner at about 9:30.
Then Jeremy said he was tired and he went to bed.
Inspector: Did you go to bed then?
Amanda: No, I didn’t. I went for a walk in the garden.
Inspector: What time did you go to bed?
Amanda: About quarter to twelve.
Inspector: Was your husband asleep?
Amanda: I don’t know, Inspector.
We…we slept in different rooms.
But I saw that his door was closed.
Inspector: Did you hear anything when you were in your room?
Amanda: Yes. I heard Jeremy’s bedroom door. It opened.
I thought it was Jeremy. Then it closed again.
I read in bed for half an hour and then I went to sleep.
Inspector: What time did you get up this morning?
Amanda: I got up at about 7:15.
I had breakfast and at eight o’clock I took a cup of tea to my husband.
I found him in bed. He was…dead.
Inspector: Tell me, Mrs. Travers, did you love your husband?
Amanda: Jeremy is…was a difficult man.
Inspector: But did you love him, Mrs. Travers?
Amanda: No, Inspector. I hated him.